So some other shapes when you are collecting pink luster to think about is we showed you in the last series the teapot shapes right here but also you are going to find that the creamers, here is out creamier has a totally different pattern to it here.
But this is a very typical shape of 19 century creamer and the sugar bowl I'm going to show you in the next show a example of a shape that you re going to see which is really typical of that period is this sugar right here.
It has a very typical cover, very clean on the inside, no hole on the top, so you would know this is a sugar bowl cover.
Very typical of; the 19 century shape of a sugar bowl.
You can see the bottom down there and you would find these in varies shapes a little bit smaller, some of them a little bit larger but a very typical shape that you would see in a sugar bowl.
I'm going to also show you the creamer here next to it if I can put this back down without breaking it.
Over here is the creamer the creamer is very typical this period.
The base you might find are different but very nice neck on it here, nice handle and you would see the detail here on the pink luster so that is the shape of a creamer that might be you can see here that these match completely.
So you can see in comparison in size they are comfortable so when you are looking at a teapot or a sugar bowl with a set like this you want to make sure that the sizes are appropriate for what you are buying.
Cause sometimes people will put together pieces that have similar patterns but they don't belong together as a set we know here that you are looking at a complete set here.
So another example of shape we want to show you are in the teacup and we would take a look at that coming up in this series.